What is this?
Bro Snake.
Let me explain.
Bro Snake,
don't get the wrong idea.
What is this?
Bro Snake,
I just got promoted, you know.
I wanted to show my appreciation.
I swear.
You know what's good for you.
That computer works best.
Get to work.
Thanks, Bro Snake.
Everyone, line up by the door!
Move it!
We've lost all contact with Sun Ming.
All we can do now
is bet on Gu Yan.
From now on,
no one is allowed to leave.
If you have to go, use the toilet here.
Bro Snake,
I'm almost done here.
Just a little bit more.
Trying to mess with me?
Listen up.
This deal today,
you have to close it.
Let's teach those cops a lesson!
Right here, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Hello, I'm at the ATM now.
Hello.
Now, find an ATM that takes deposits,
and insert your bank card.
Tell me your card number,
and you will be able to receive the funds.
Okay.
My card number is 622363...
Captain Sun, Huang Shanshan is brilliant.
She's her village's only college student.
Her dad borrowed her tuition door-to-door.
Combined with her financial aid,
it barely got her into college.
If she loses this money,
the consequences will be unimaginable.
Does her family know where she went?
Her mother said
she went to the ATM closest to her home.
Xiao Lin has locked onto her location.
We need to hurry.
We have started the process on our end.
Please wait a moment.
Please check your balance
to see if the funds have arrived.
Hello, the money hasn't arrived yet.
Miss, please do not worry.
Please remove your card and try again.
Okay.
How is it, miss?
Has it arrived?
I still haven't received the subsidy.
There might be an issue with this card.
Miss, do you have any other bank cards?
Yes, I have one sent by the school.
The bank card for tuition fees.
Please try again with this card.
Hello, it still doesn't work.
Miss, I just checked.
As for this card of yours,
it does support receiving funds.
It just has not been activated yet.
Does this card have a balance?
Yes, it does.
It has 10,000 yuan.
Miss, let us do this.
You transfer 9,900 yuan
to our Education Bureau's official account.
to activate the offline receiving function.
In the future,
you will not need to visit a bank for it.
Why do I still need to make a transfer?
The Trojan system is already in her phone.
Miss, just do this for now.
Log into our Education Bureau's account.
And enter your name.
Work badge.
Miss, please take a look.
This is my work badge.
Are you reassured now?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
I just wanted to be careful.
It is good to be cautious.
I completely understand.
But we are getting off work soon.
The next steps are quite complicated.
I am afraid of delaying your schooling.
How about this.
I will cancel it for you first.
You think about it first.
Tell me after you have thought it through.
Okay?
No, wait!
Don't cancel it.
Screw it.
I'll crash these scammers' system first.
Miss, if you do not think for yourself,
you must think of your parents.
This is the last batch of subsidies.
If you miss it, it will truly be gone.
Hurry.
Any updates?
Captain Sun, Huang Shanshan won't answer.
Is it that ATM up ahead?
That's the one.
Let's go.
Huang Shanshan, don't transfer the money!
What are you doing?
We are the Anti-Fraud Police.
The person you're talking to is a scammer.
That can't be.
They're from the Education Bureau.
The number you dialed is not in service.
How could this happen?
That was my dad's life-saving money.
Huang Shanshan.
Please don't panic.
We'll definitely help you get it back.
I'm so stupid.
Xiao Hui, help her get some rest.
Bro Snake, the money's in.
Not bad, Bro Liu.
Well done.
A flying start.
No matter how fast the cops are,
they're not as fast as us.
The top ten performers today
will each get a 50,000 bonus.
Club!
Hot models!
The bottom five performers
will be locked in the dark room.
Shanshan!
Shanshan, Shanshan!
Ma'am, you can't go in.
We will do everything we can to save her.
Please calm down first.
You have to save my daughter!
She worked so hard to get into college.
Why is our daughter's life so hard?
Here are the new files.
Give me another batch.
You better hurry up.
You're the only one falling behind now.
Alright.
My neck is sore from sitting so long.
Give me another batch.
I'll help you one last time.
When I need you,
I'll give you a signal.
Sitting here coding all day,
my neck is about to break.
You got a death wish?
Toilet!
Bro Snake!
What the hell?
I can't hold it!
Seriously?
You're even fighting over the toilet?
How do you use this thing?
Let me out!
Help!
I will do my best!
I will work hard!
I must give it my all!
I must succeed!
This is more like it!
Li Wen.
You need to step it up.
You're a genius programmer.
Your numbers need to beat Bro Liu's.
Yes, Bro Snake.
Why are you so nervous?
I...